the world is responding to kovat 19 at
Sun Life we're doing our part to our
family of companies gave more than two
million dollars to food health and elder
care we donated life insurance and
deferred or reduced individual premiums
if needed more than 95 percent of our
employees are working from home to keep
serving clients and advisors are always
here to help you
we're pretty money back into the economy
at this time we're innovating in real
time with data-driven insights new
virtual healthcare services and ongoing
communications are serving people at
home so they can focus on what matters
most health protecting loved ones having
the means to live their lives the best
way possible it's why Sun Life has been
here for more than a hundred and fifty
five years will rise through this -
together
[Music]